There are many different types of houses in the UK.
英国的房屋类型丰富多样。
You may see detached, semi-detached, terraced houses or even end-of-terrace houses on a typical street.
在一条普通的街道上，你可能会看到独栋别墅、双拼别墅、连排别墅，甚至是排屋端头房。
You might see mansions in more affluent parts of town, or people residing in bungalows, preferring to live a life without stairs.
在城镇的富人区，你会见到各式豪宅；也有人选择住在平房里，就为了省去爬楼梯的麻烦。
Quaint cottages may dot the countryside, while heading to the cities you could see any number of types of flats, including houses turned into converted flats, studios and duplexes.
古雅别致的乡村小屋星罗棋布地点缀着乡间田野，而在城市里，公寓的种类更是五花八门，包括由民宅改建而成的公寓、单身公寓以及复式公寓。
But one thing you will notice is that many houses come from different eras, and asking a British person about their ideal home, many of them will have a specific period property in mind.
不过有一点你肯定会发现，英国的许多房屋都来自不同的历史时期，要是问起英国人心中的理想居所，很多人都会想到某一种特定的老式建筑。
For some, it could be Victorian houses, which are often seen with bay windows, high ceilings, stained glass doors and coloured brickwork.
对有些人来说，理想居所就是维多利亚时期的房子。这类房子通常带有凸窗、高挑的天花板、彩色玻璃门和彩色砖石外墙。
During the Victorian era, a huge number of houses, particularly terraced, were built in towns and cities to accommodate vast numbers of workers who were moving from more rural areas.
维多利亚时代，城镇里建造了大量房屋，尤其是连排别墅，目的是为了容纳大批从乡村迁居而来的务工人员。
Georgian architecture refers to houses built during the period of 1714 and 1830 during the reigns of four British monarchs, all called George.
乔治王朝风格建筑指的是1714年至1830年间建造的房屋，这一时期正值英国四位名为乔治的君主相继统治。
Usually houses with this architectural style have a more symmetrical theme, both internally and externally, with a small square garden in front.
这类风格的房屋通常内外设计都更讲究对称，门前还配有一方小巧的庭院。
For those not into older properties, new builds from the 1990s onwards offer better insulation against the cold and newer electrics.
对于不喜欢老式建筑的人而言，20世纪90年代以后建成的新房有着更好的防寒保温效果和更新的电路系统。
And those who prefer less maintenance could always go with the open-plan or minimalist look of the modern era.
而那些偏爱少费心打理房屋的人，则可以选择现代风格的开放式或极简主义住宅。
So whether it’s high ceilings, better insulation, brickwork, bungalows or square gardens, people in Britain have a wide variety of preferences when it comes to where they live.
所以，不管是偏爱高挑的天花板、良好的保温效果、砖石外墙、平房还是方形庭院，英国人对于居所的喜好可谓各不相同。
And their ideal home may just simply be a case of what style feels like home.
而他们心中的理想之家，说到底不过是一种能让人找到家的归属感的建筑风格罢了。